hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Hey, Akamaru!
Wait up, Akamaru.
Akamaru!
Naruto...
I made you a box lunch.
Eat it if you like.
Oh, thanks.
What's this?
What the heck's the idea, you guys...?
This isn't a picnic.
I'm sorry.
Come on, it's okay.
It's an easy mission
the three of us can manage.
You said yourself
you weren't fired up, right?
MISSION CHECK IN
I'm not fired up!
It's a mission to catch a petty thief.
It'd be the same no matter
who went on the mission.
Look. Under normal circumstances,
a three-man team of Kiba, Hinata
and Shino would be fundamental.
But unfortunately, Shino is absent
as he's off on a different mission.
It'd be better if even you were there
than not, right?
What, Old Lady?!
That's taking it too far!
I'll do my best.
This is a mission I kind of
can't get into, though.
There's probably no need to take
the trouble to determine a troop leader.
Anyway, your mission is
to capture the man who stole
the Misogi tea jar owned by
the feudal lord of the Land of Tea.
This man, Gosunkugi.
According to sources,
he's now hiding in the Land of Stone.
Get over there lickety-split
and catch him lickety-split.
Hearing that makes me feel
less fired up than ever.
Here, Akamaru.
Well, missions like this are okay
once in a while, right?
Let's take it easy.
It's an easy mission, so all the more
reason I want to finish it up quick.
What'll happen if the Pervy Sage
comes back while I'm gone?
I'm sorry, Naruto.
I... I was so happy to be
on a mission... with you.
Huh? What did you say, Hinata?
I can't hear you.
What are you blushing for?
You're a weird one.
Well, hold your horses... Look.
We'll be in the Land of Stone
once we cross that mountain pass.
Be sure to fortify yourself
with food by then.
It's kind of complicated
when it's like eating myself.
Hey, this is good!
Hinata, you'd make a great wife!
What?
Wife...?
This is the first post station
of the Land of Stone.
Doesn't it look... kind of rough?
Friend or Foe!
Bounty Hunter of the Wild
What are these guys doing...
staring like that?
This doesn't feel like
we'll be able to do this lickety-split.
What is it, Akamaru?
Could it be that Gosunkugi guy
is among them?
Got you, Gosunkugi!
"WANTED"
It's a photo.
What, this is Gosunkugi, isn't it?
{"REWARD THREE MILLION RYO"
Three million ryo?
What's the meaning of this?
Look... They're hanging over there,
and here, too.
All right, I'll try asking someone.
Hello!
Can I help you?
I have something I'd like to ask you.
What, if you're not a customer, beat it.
Then I'll order something...
I'll have ramen.
I'll have a hamburger steak with cheese.
He'll have milk.
This is funny. Milk?
Hamburger steak with cheese?
And ramen on top of that?
Are you making a fool of me?
Get out, brats!
If it's the money, we have some.
That's not the issue.
Oh... It's dangerous for kids
to carry such a large amount of money...
I'll take charge of it for you.
After all, there are lots of bad men
in this town.
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you still in?
Oh, just a minute.
I got the money. I'll be right over.
What's with you? Hey, let go!
You're the one who'll let go.
How about that?
You brat... You want to fight?!
That's the plan... Bring it!
You punk!
Hold it, Naruto.
Naruto, look around.
This is bad.
Master, milk.
Who the hell are you?
Okay, coming right up!
Here you are.
Thanks.
Now, no need to hesitate.
Drink up.
It's a treat from
old billiard-ball head over there.
"Billiard-ball head" means me?
Knock it off, you jerk!
Who would treat some puppy milk?
You want to get killed?!
Bounty, Michizo Manaka.
You can take the credit, Master.
Take the money for the milk
from his bounty...
And the money to repair the table, too.
I don't need change.
He's strong.
Are you in the same trade as I am?
Sorry about that.
Wait!
Something you want?
Who the heck are you, old man?
"Old man" you say?
I'm Sazanami, a bounty hunter.
How cool!
Old man!
Say, say...
That thing earlier was cool.
The iai-nuki?
It was so fast I couldn't see when
you drew your sword.
It was really surprising.
I bet that's what they mean
when they say "In a blink of an eye."
Life and death is on the line
for us bounty hunters...
No matter how many lives we can have,
it wouldn't be enough
if we couldn't draw our sword
faster than others.
Say, say! Say, say!
What's a bounty hunter?
Let's see...
There are people who offer a bounty
in order to capture bad guys.
And a bounty hunter catches
those bad guys and receives the bounty.
Then this guy has
a bounty on him, right?
Boy, that's...
Why's there so much money on his head?
This guy's just a simple thief...
A simple thief, you say?
Boy, this guy's a super A-rank bounty
who has killed dozens of people
for the sake of stealing.
What?!
No way.
Say what?
What's the meaning of this?
I haven't heard about that.
The feudal lord who commissioned
this mission
might not have known about that.
Mission?
Yeah. We're Hidden Leaf Ninja
and we came to this town
to capture Gosunkugi.
Leaf?
So you're ninja, huh?
This is interesting.
So even kids like this
are qualified to be ninja?
What?! Don't make fun of us!
Well, don't get so mad.
Sorry about that...
I'll treat you guys to something. Milk?
We're not Akamaru. I want ramen!
Then I'll have a hamburger steak
with cheese.
I guess I'll have ramen, too.
Okay. Come with me.
Jeez, no way would there be
ramen in a bar.
Hey, old man. Would even miso ramen
topped with pork be okay?
Sure, have anything you like.
What is this? We're rapidly moving away
from town.
I don't see a ramen shop anywhere.
Now then...
I don't see any ramen shops.
So what I said earlier about treating
you guys is cancelled.
Sorry, but you guys are going to die here.
Old man...
You guys are going to die here.
Hey, old man... What's the idea?
To think you guys would know
that Gosunkugi is in this town.
So what if we do know?
Gosunkugi is my prey.
I can't hand him over to you.
Knock it off!
You should just go get him yourself.
No, even if you guys are kids,
it's a different story when it comes
to Leaf Ninja.
It's better to have fewer...
Wait, no competitors.
Old man.
Here I go.
Hinata!
That's dirty!
Naruto!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry:
All-Four Jutsu!
Interesting.
Bring it.
I won't lose at speed!
Damn it! Where are you?
Too slow.
Boy...
Now you're the last one.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Oh...
I won't let you do as you please!
Over here!
You're mine.
Almost.
Forgive me, boy.
I'll be the one to defeat him,
no matter what.
Akamaru.
Damn it! He got us good.
Hinata, you okay?
Yeah.
Where's Sazanami?
Could it be he went after Gosunkugi?
I can't just sit here like this!
He'll beat us to the draw.
Damn it! Where is that old man?
Did he leave town?
Going after Gosunkugi?
Akamaru, we're counting on you!
The most crucial treasure is missing here.
Filthy hyena.
I waited a long time
for you to make your move.
Unfortunately, I have
an important job to do.
Time is valuable.
I'll get right to taking care of you.
Ninja Art: Torpedo Nail.
Gosunkugi, here I come!
You can't move anymore.
It's over.
Finish him.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Gosunkugi, you're under arrest!
Damn it. Reinforcements, huh?
Retreat!
I won't let you get away!
Wait.
Boy...
You must not go.
Old man!
Hey, Old Man Sazanami.
Stay away from him.
He's too much for you guys.
How could such a strong guy be beaten?
Gosunkugi isn't a mere thief.
He's a Shinobi, same as us.
Shinobi.
Sazanami!
Is this one of Gosunkugi's comrades?
You! As I recall,
you were in the bar before...
Damn!
Who was that guy?
What?
A wanted flyer.
Did he mistake us for Gosunkugi?
No, that's not it.
"This man who calls himself Tokichi
is a major criminal
who has killed a family of three..."
"He has a bird-shaped birthmark
on his chest."
A bird-shaped birthmark...?
It couldn't be...
What is it, Hinata?
I can't tell because
his face is covered with scars...
But he has... a bird-shaped birthmark.
He has a bounty on his head, too?
What the heck is going on
with everything?
dokomademo tsudzuku michi ni wa ironna koto arunda ne
so many things happen on this endless road, right?
tsuyogari na kimi ga kyou wa juwaki koshi ni namida koe
although you're strong-willed your voice wavered on the phone today
donna yume oikakete kokomade kitan darou
what dreams did you chase to get here?
wakara na kunattari suru koto wa boku ni datte aru kara nee BABY
even I have times when I just don't understand baby
kimi ga namida no toki ni wa boku ga soba ni iru kara
when you're sad I'll be close to you
hanareba nare no yoru datte boku wa soba ni iru kara
even on nights when we're apart I'll be close to you
boku wa soba ni iru kara
I'll be close to you
A long, long time ago just recently on an overcast clear day...
It was night since morning.
The righteous rogue Sazanami's string of his past unwinds and frays.
Ah, the fatal foe Gosunkugi!
Although the situation is now clear to me,
there are times when a Shinobi cannot back out!
Hey, hey, hey, Gosunkungi!
Give it up and submit to arrest!
Next time:
"Catch or be Caught?! Showdown at the OK Temple."